Guide to the Joseph Torchia papers M1694
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 3: Biographical/Ephemera
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - La Cancha Workout (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Graphic Source Clip Art (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - No Escape draft (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Cassette tape Envelopes (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Flannery O'Connor (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Flannery O'Connor (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Napa Valley Appellation (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Kryptonite Kid performance/discussion text & cassettes (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Kryptonite Kid performance/discussion cassettes (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - The Kryptonite Kid flyer (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - University of Florida (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Esquire Magazine (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - The Fifth Dimension (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The Fifth Dimension (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Nespaper article Gay Sunshine (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - The Kryptonite Kid notebook (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Negative of Hogan Review of "K. Kid" (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Superman Comics (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Finding Life in 'Death Valley' (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous MAterial (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Best Sellers, March 18, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco Chronicle February 26, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Bay Area Reporter Article (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - People Weekly, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Graysmith (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Brian Hatch (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Hitachi TV (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Frank Holbrook Miscellaneous Material (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - An elegant celebration of Christmas (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Material from Jamie Jobb (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Jell-O Girl gives a party, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Newsclippings (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Comic books (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Article (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper article: Album (S.F.) (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper article: America's Best (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper article: Army Recruiter (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper article: Artisits (Angelo + Holbrook) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper article: Big Brothers (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper article: Bingo (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper article: Blackpoint Music Festival (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Magazine: Maupin (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper article: McDonald's (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper article: Meals on wheels (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper article: Mean Streets (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper article (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper article: Model A (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper article: Monster of spell (Janette Moss) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper article: Magle, Gunther (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper article: Newley, Tony (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper article: New Year's (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper article: Nose (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper article: Outreach (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper article: Perverted Fauna (Advocate) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper article: Pets Magazine (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper article: Pinska, Klarna (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper article: Poppers (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper article: Pool Hall (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper article: Possessions (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper article: Poverello (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Contacts (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Dimp Heap 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Promo (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper article: Blagburn, Sara (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper article: Cafe Flore (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper article: Peter Caputo (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper article: Cartoonist (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper article: Carol Channing (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper article: Children's Hospital (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper article: Children's Theatre (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper article: Chimney Sweep (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper article: Chinatown (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper article: Christmas in the Tenderloin (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper article: Cigar Bands (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper article: Close Encounters (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper article: Coffee (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper article: Corporate Airplanes (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper article: Cowboys (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper article: Deanna Crowe (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper article: Deanna Cruikshank (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper article: Curfews (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper article: Dakin (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper article: Dickens (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper article: Dirty-Book Store (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper article: Dirty-Book Store (Examiner) (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper article: Disco (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper article: Virginia Duncan (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper article: Earthquake (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper article: Erkshire (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper article: Experts (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper article: 'Fag Attack' (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper article: Farm Family (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper article: Clarita Fazzari (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper article: Ferlinghetti (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper article: Flores, Joe (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper article: The Floss (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper article: Jerry Ford (Carter) (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper article: (Underground Man) (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper article: Greyhound (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper article: Hall of Justice (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper article: The "Heritage" (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper article: Holmes (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper article: John Holmes (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper article: Home Movies (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper article: Jack Jones (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper article: Ron Jones (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper article: Juanita (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper article: Kearney (Buddhist) (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper article: Sandy Leeds (Dancer) (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper article: Lesbian Priest (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper article: Ernest Lloyd (7th-day Adventure) (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper article: Matlovich (Ex-Sgt. Leonard) (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - The Edible Variety T.E.V. Contract (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - First Communion (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Gay Murders (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Various Manuscripts by: D. Patrick Haley? (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Holt Rinehart & Winston, royalty statements (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ernest Hemingway, interview by George Plimpton (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sex Change in Snails: Research Material (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Notebook regarding Kryptonite Kid? (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Notebook regarding Kryptonite Kid? (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Notebook regarding Kryptonite Kid? (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Notebook regarding Kryptonite Kid? (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - A treasure Album of Milledgeville and Baldwin County, Georgia (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Superman (Clips) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Superman ephemera (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Punk (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Clippings: Richard III (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: Road Food (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Santa (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Clippings: Sex Surrogates (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Clippings: Shoplifting (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Clippings: Smoking (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Clippings: Stock Watchers (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Clippings: Street Preachers (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Trapeze (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Clipping: Underwear (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Clipping: Woolworth (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - "The Kryptonite Kid" Clips (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Jane (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Personal: roladex cards of contact information (Card-box 41)
  - History of Comics, vol. 1 [highlighted - potential source for Kryptonite Kid] (Flat-box 43, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous newspapers (Flat-box 44)
  - Christopher Street (Carton 47, Folder 20)
- Series 4: Artwork/Graphic Production
  - Sketchbooks; artwork (Flat-box 39)
  - Artwork (Flat-box 43, Folder 2-3)
  - Graphic Production materials (Flat-box 40)
- Series 5: Media
  - Audiocassettes; computer disks (Carton 45)
- Series 6: Financial Records
  - Tax/Business records (Carton 46)
- Series 7: Accession 2012-134
  - Peoples Temple to Joseph Torchia, 12/24/1976 (Half-box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lawrence Ferlinghetti (Half-box 1, Folder 2)
  - Valenti Angels (Half-box 1, Folder 3)
  - David Plante (Half-box 1, Folder 4)
  - Guggenheim (Half-box 1, Folder 5)
  - Millicent Dillon (Half-box 1, Folder 6)